http://www.cvsmedia.co.uk/shop/privacy.html

Categories
Bundle Deals Plasma Screens LCD Screens Projectors Projector Screens Projector Lamps Audio Furniture Interactive Accessories AV Separates Cases Installation Warranty Upgrades Clearance Items
Special OffersFeatured ProductsNew Products
Shopping Cart
0 items
Quick Find
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for.Advanced Search
Manufacturers
Please Select3MAcerAcoustic EnergyAKGAnchorApartAPOApolloAQUiVOArcherASKAustralian MonitorAverMediaB-TechBarcoBeamaxBenqBoston AcousticsBoxlightBushCanonCasioChameleonClearOneCombiflexCTXCVSMediaD-TexDa-LiteDASDellDENONDNPDrapereBeamEikiEpsonErgoMountsEzClickGeneeGlimmGoo SystemsGSPGyrationHarman KardonHCLHitachiIiyamaInfinityInfocusInstallationsInteractive Technolo..JamoJBLJoytechJVCKEFKISSKobeLabtechLG ElectronicsLogitechMarantzMarkantMatroxMediumMimioMitsubishiMovieluxNECNumarkNumonicsNUVUOmniMountOptikineticsOptomaORIONPanasonicPanoviewPasoPhilipsPhonicPioneerPlasmaBoyPolyVisionProjectaProximaQSCRaw InternationalRothSaharaSamsungSanyoSapphireScreen InternationalScreen LabsSeleco'SennheiserSharpShureSMSSonorousSonyStarelloStarflexTannoyToshibaUmaxUNICOLViewsonicVisionVogelsWeibel Lift AGYamaha
Specials
234cm x 132cm (106") Panoview Manual Screen DISCONTINUED 16:9 Matte White DISCONTINUED£158.95£98.70
Latest News
Paramount and Dreamworks Drop Blu-ray ThemeSceneÂ® HD80 - Seen as Scene Perfect! Sapphire Screens introduce new Electric Floor Screen to the market.
Latest News Blog
Reviews
We have bought several lamps from cvsmedia, usually delivere ..
Information
Info Pages
Special Offers
Featured Products
List New ProductsList All ProductsList All CategoriesList All ManufacturersShipping & ReturnsPrivacy NoticeConditions of UseTerms & ConditionsContact UsLinksAnti Spam
Privacy Notice
CVSMedia.co.uk takes the privacy of its customers very seriously. Please read the following policy to understand how we will treat your personal information when you use our site. If this policy changes then we will let you know via updated information listed at the bottom of this page, and will give you the opportunity to opt out of any changes which affect you.THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT:In order to provide you with the best Internet experience we can, we collect certain personal information about you. When you register for our monthly newsletter and personalise it to your requirements we will store your email address together with any other information you may provide as part of the personalisation process. When you buy anything via the site, we may need to collect information about you to process the transaction and fulfil your order. This information may include, but is not limited to, details such as your name, your address and your credit card details. When you view our site by linking from another web page we may store the name of that web page for purposes of internal administration.WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?CVSMedia.co.uk uses your personal information to provide you with the best online experience and to provide you with a personalised service to give you details of offers, which we think will be of interest to you. If you have chosen to receive them, we will also use your information to provide you with our monthly newsletter and other email alerts letting you stay up-to-date about relevant offers. We may also use the information to process any transactions you undertake with us and for internal administration and analysis. We disclose your information to third parties only for the purpose of completing your transaction with us, providing the above services to you and for the purposes of associated administration and obtaining professional advice. We do not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes.COOKIESCookies are small files, which are sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard disc. If you have registered with cvsmedia.co.uk, then your computer will store an identifying code in the cookie which means you do not need to type in your email address each time you return to the site. Other than this, we do not store your password or any other information in the cookie, or use it for any other purpose.DATA PROTECTIONIn the UK we operate and are registered in accordance with applicable data protection legislation.CONSENTBy disclosing your personal information to us using this website or over the telephone, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by CVSMedia.co.uk in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.CONTACT USIf you still have any concerns about privacy or security, please contact us at: info@cvsmedia.co.uk
Thursday 11th of October 2007 07:24:55 AM
3455891 requests since Monday 09 August, 2004
Telephone Orders: 0845 644 1904Email Orders: sales@cvsmedia.co.ukwww.cvsmedia.co.uk | www.ourhomecinema.co.uk | www.medialamps.co.uk | www.medialamps.comwww.lampmodule.co.uk | www.lampmodule.com | www.lampsareus.co.uk | www.lampsuk.comwww.lampsuk.co.uk | www.projector-bulb.co.uk | www.projectorsbulbs.comwww.projectorsbulbs.co.uk | www.projector-lamps.orgCopyright © 2007 CVS Production SuppliesPowered by osCommerce
